[{"Response":"Definitely agree","Percentage of respondents":27.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that your local area is a place where people from different backgrounds get on well together?"},{"Response":"Tend to agree","Percentage of respondents":54.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that your local area is a place where people from different backgrounds get on well together?"},{"Response":"Tend to disagree","Percentage of respondents":8.9,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that your local area is a place where people from different backgrounds get on well together?"},{"Response":"Definitely disagree","Percentage of respondents":4.6,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that your local area is a place where people from different backgrounds get on well together?"},{"Response":"Strongly agree","Percentage of respondents":20.2,"Question":"The friendships and associations I have with other people in my neighbourhood mean a lot to me"},{"Response":"Agree","Percentage of respondents":37.6,"Question":"The friendships and associations I have with other people in my neighbourhood mean a lot to me"},{"Response":"Neither agree nor disagree","Percentage of respondents":26.1,"Question":"The friendships and associations I have with other people in my neighbourhood mean a lot to me"},{"Response":"Disagree","Percentage of respondents":8.4,"Question":"The friendships and associations I have with other people in my neighbourhood mean a lot to me"},{"Response":"Strongly disagree","Percentage of respondents":5.7,"Question":"The friendships and associations I have with other people in my neighbourhood mean a lot to me"},{"Response":"Strongly agree","Percentage of respondents":12.7,"Question":"If I needed advice about something I could go to someone in my neighbourhood -"},{"Response":"Agree","Percentage of respondents":34.7,"Question":"If I needed advice about something I could go to someone in my neighbourhood -"},{"Response":"Neither agree nor disagree","Percentage of respondents":19.2,"Question":"If I needed advice about something I could go to someone in my neighbourhood -"},{"Response":"Disagree","Percentage of respondents":18.6,"Question":"If I needed advice about something I could go to someone in my neighbourhood -"},{"Response":"Strongly disagree","Percentage of respondents":11.7,"Question":"If I needed advice about something I could go to someone in my neighbourhood -"}]